《迷失》前情提要...
Previously on "lost"...
你怎么会认识我父亲
How did you know my father?
他过来看他女儿
He came to see his daughter.
我女儿也在那架飞机上
My daughter was on your plane.
她叫Claire
Her name was Claire.
我们过来各取一份
We're here to get a blood sample from you
-你和你儿子Aaron的血液样本  -为什么
- And one from your son aaron. - Why?
以确定你和这个孩子的关系
To determine your relationship to the child.
你要去哪  妈妈
Where you going, mommy?
我们去度假  宝贝
We're going on vacation, baby.
等等  你在洛杉矶吗  我当然有时间见面
Wait, you're in l.a.? Of course I can meet, yeah.
你好  Kate
Hello, Kate.
-你怎么样  -扶我上车
- You okay? - Get me to the car.
-Sayid  你被袭击了  -Hurley在哪
- Sayid, you've been attacked. - Where's Hurley?
John  拯救这座岛的唯一方法
The only way to save the island, John,
就是让你的人回来
Is to get your people back here.
我应该怎么做
How? How am I supposed to do that?
-怎么了  -你...
- What? - You've...
你知道我这是怎么了吗
Do you know what's happening to me?
Charlotte  Charlotte
Charlotte? Charlotte?
不用这么蹑手蹑脚的
Oh, you don't have to whisper.
他睡着了就没关系了
When he's out, he's out.
总算有个人能睡得着了
At least one of us can sleep.
我至少得花上两个晚上
It's gonna take more than two nights
才能习惯在普通的床上睡觉
For me to get used to sleeping in a normal bed.
我们该拿他怎么办
What are we gonna do about him?
我是说Aaron
About Aaron.
我不知道
I don't know.
我反复考虑过关于他的问题
I've been thinking a lot about him.
你知道Clair曾经去过洛杉矶
Did you know that Claire was flying to l.a.
-打算让别人收养他吗  -我不知道
- To give him up for adoption? - No. No, I didn't.
我觉得应该对外宣称他是我儿子
I think we should say he's mine.
-什么  -我们可以说我在被捕的时候
- What? - We could say that I was six months pregnant
已经有六个月身孕
When I was arrested
然后我在岛上生下了他
And that I gave birth to him on the island.
- 没人会知道的  -Kate  不   你不必...
- No one would ever know.- Kate, no. You don't have to...
一定还有其它的办法
There's other ways to do this.
我们已经失去了他们  Michael  Jin Sawyer...
After everyone we've lost-- Michael, Jin, Sawyer...
我不能再失去他
I can't lose him, too.
Sawyer并没有死
Sawyer's not dead.
是
No.
但他已经远去了
But he's gone.
晚安  Jack
Good night, Jack.
Kate
Kate...
如果我们想安全获救
If we're gonna be safe,
如果我们想保护留在岛上的其他人
If we're gonna protect the people that we left behind,
明天一早  我就要去
Tomorrow morning, I'm gonna have to
说服大家编造谎言
Convince everyone to lie.
但凭我一己之力  是无法说服他们的
If it's just me, they're never gonna go for it.
所以我首先要说服你
So I'm gonna turn to you first.
你支持我吗
Are you with me?
我一直都是支持你的
I have always been with you.
三年后
Three Years Later
合身吗
How does it fit?
很合身  谢谢你借我穿
It's perfect. Thank you for the loaner.
你穿上真不错
Looks great on you.
-你确定要这么做吗  -这可是你的主意
- Are you sure you want to do this? - It was your idea.
妈妈
Mommy!
Aaron宝贝  妈妈要出去办点事
Aaron, honey, mommy's gonna run out and do an errand.
我很快就回来  然后我们就回家
I'll be right back. Okay? And then we can go home.
别担心我们  Kate
Don't worry about us, Kate.
冰箱里有糖果  还有许多电视节目
There's candy in the minibar and a hundred channels on tv.
我们在这里会很好的
We're going to be just fine here.
Sun
Sun...
真不知道没有你我该怎么办
I don't know what I would've done if you weren't here.
谢谢你
Thank you.
这是朋友该做的
It's what any friend would do.
好了  我很快就回来
Okay, well, I will be back soon.
你和Sun好好相处
Okay, you be good for Sun.
好吗  亲爱的
Okay, honey?
祝你好运
Good luck.
这是给你的  Kwon小姐
Delivery for you, Ms. Kwon.
-谢谢你  -谢谢
- Thank you. - Thanks.
我去去就来  宝贝
I'll be right back, honey.
本字幕由YYeTs人人影视原创翻译制作
最新最快的美剧 请登陆 www.YYeTs.net
■
翻译： 宝宝宝  daisy静    Adam的范范    blackeyepea
翻译：  rosemaryai   字幕总监：非燕
■
时间轴： shawnliu87    七色九天    校对：  许愿
Charlotte  Charlotte
Charlotte? Charlotte?
到底是怎么回事
What the hell's wrong with her?
她已经昏过去十分钟了
She's been out for ten minutes.
别嚷嚷了  James
Stop shouting, James.
给你
Hey, man.
谢谢
Thank you.
如果你知道什么情况  Daniel
If there's something that you want to tell me, Daniel,
最好现在就说
Now would be a good time.
我不太明白你的意思
I'm not sure what you mean exactly.
她问你是否知道你女朋友昏迷的原因
She's asking if you know why your girlfriend had a seizure.
让我们单独谈谈  好吗
Give us some space, would you?
她之所以会这样  都是因为闪光不断出现
She's like this 'cause the sky keeps lighting up.
他明知道会这样
He knew this would happen
-却连个屁都不放...-James
- And he didn't say squat about it. - James...
走开
Go away.
你知道会发生这种情况吗
Did you know that this would happen?
我认为...
I thought...
我认为有可能
I thought it might.
我觉得这是神经学现象
I think it's neurological.
人的大脑有一个内部生物钟
Our brains have an internal clock,
对时间的意识
A sense of time.
这些闪光...扰乱了生物钟
The flashes... throw the clock off.
就像时差混乱
It's like really bad jet lag.
但时差混乱不会致人出血  Daniel
Really bad jet lag doesn't make you hemorrhage, Daniel.
你知道为什么我们其它人没有这种情况吗
You wanna tell me why it isn't happening to the rest of us?
不知道
I don't know.
幸好没有
But thank god it's not.
谢谢你的耐心等候
Thank you for waiting.
我的助理好好招待你了吗
Did my assistant offer you something to drink?
是的  很好  谢谢
Um, yes. I'm fine, thank you.
很好  Austen小姐  请坐
Good. Please, Ms. Austen, sit.
那么
So...
有什么问题
How can I help you?
Norton先生
Mr. Norton,
当你到我家来取我和我儿子
When you came to my house looking for blood samples
血液样本时
From me and my son,
我问你的客户是谁
I asked you who your client was...
我说无法透露
And I said I couldn't tell you.
对  我想和你作个交易
Yeah. I'm here to offer you a deal.
我把血液样本给你
I'll give you the blood samples,
但是  我想先和你的客户谈谈
But first, I wanna talk to your client.
考虑到你的要求
Considering what you're asking for,
这样的做法更合理
That's more than reasonable.
好吧  我一会要和客户见面
Well, I am, uh, seeing my client later today,
我一定把你的要求转述给他
And I will be sure to pass along your offer.
但是我很确定答案将会是
But I am pretty sure of what the answer's gonna be--
不行
No.
至于原因  当然是
And the reason, of course,
你没有任何资格来谈条件
Is that you're in no position to be making any kind of deals,
而我们都清楚
And we both know it.
我这里有一份已经签署的法庭命令可以强制你
I have a signed court order compelling you
允许我们核实你是否是孩子的母亲
To let us confirm that you're the child's mother.
我完全可以今天就派地方司法官去执行
I could send the sheriff over there today and make you do it,
但是我的客户坚持要求我们
But my client insists that we...
私下转移监护权
Handle the exchange of custody quietly.
你说的"转移监护权"是什么意思
What do you mean "exchange of custody"?
你完全明白我是什么意思
You know exactly what I mean.
不  我
No, I...
Norton先生
Mr. Norton,
我只是想知道谁会这样对我
I just wanna know who is doing this to me.
你自食其果
You did this to yourself.
现在是时候做准备了  Austen小姐
Now it is time you prepare yourself, Ms. Austen.
你将会失去这个男孩
You are going to lose the boy.
我们必须回到兰花站那里去
We have to go back to the Orchid.
什么
Excuse me?
兰花站
The Orchid.
那是一切开始的地方  也许会是终结的地方
That's where all this started. maybe it's where it'll all stop.
温室离这里很远
That greenhouse is a long ways away.
你说过你在后面的海滩有艘zodiac的救生艇
You said you had a zodiac raft back at the beach.
我们可以坐那艇  从小岛的角落抄近路过去
We could take that, cut around the horn of the island,
只要花一半的时间
Be at the orchid in half the time.
让我猜猜,到了那里你一定知道我们该怎么做
And let me guess. You know exactly what to do when we get there.
不  一点都不知道
No, not exactly at all,
但是我知道Ben就是用它离开这个岛的
But I know that Ben used it to leave the island.
如果我照样做  我们也可以得救
And if I can do the same thing, I believe I can save us.
那你要怎么做呢
And how you gonna do that?
这里发生的一切都是因为他们离开了
This is all happening because they left.
我认为如果把他们带回来  这一切就会停止
I think it'll stop if I can bring them back.
-把谁带回来  -Jack  Sun  Sayid  Hugo  Kate
- Bring who back? - Jack, Sun, Sayid, Hugo, Kate.
船炸毁了  而直升机很可能在上面
The boat blew up, and that chopper was probably on it.
他们没有死  James
They're not dead, James.
-谁说的  -那无关紧要
- Says who? - That doesn't matter.
重要的是他们会回来
All that matters is they've gotta come back.
我必须让他们回来
I have to make them come back...
即使会让我丧命
Even if it kills me.
你不想让他们回来吗  James
Don't you want 'em to come back, James?
你不想让她回来吗
Don't you want her to come back?
我想什么无关紧要
It doesn't matter what I want.
她醒了
She's waking up!
你还好吗
Are you okay?
你是谁
Who are you?
是我啊
It's me.
Danniel啊
It's daniel.
Daniel
Daniel.
我的头
Oh, my head.
怎么了
What happened?
又来了一次闪光  你晕倒了
There was another flash. you passed out.
感觉怎么样
How do you feel?
有点儿晕  但是
A bit dizzy, but...
我还好
I'm fine.
很好
Good.
好啊  一切恢复正常了
Hooray. Everything's back to normal.
现在怎么办
Now what?
我告诉你怎么办
I'll tell you "now what."
我们要回兰花站
We're going to the orchid.
瞳孔扩张基本恢复正常
Dilation's almost back to normal.
真好  把输液管给我拔下来然后出发
Good. Now take this i.v. out of my arm, and let's go.
Sayid  你已经失去知觉42个小时
Sayid, you were unconscious for 42 hours.
你的身体里的镇定剂相当于一匹马用的三倍
You had the equivalent of three doses of horse tranquilizer In your system.
如果你已经派那个人去Hurley家
If you sent that man to Hurley's house,
我们现在就得离开
we have to leave now.
你需要放松  Ben不会伤害Hurley
You need to relax. Ben is not gonna hurt Hurley.
Ben是我们一伙的
Ben is on our side.
他只和自己一伙
The only side he's on is his own.
Shephard医生
Dr. Shephard?
我是Ariza医生  临床治疗主管
I'm Dr. Ariza, director of clinical services.
能和你说句话吗
A word with you, please?
我马上就回来
I'll be right back.
你知道自己在干什么
What do you think you are doing here?
我在治疗病人
I was treating a patient.
我道歉  这是急诊
I apologize. It was an emergency.
我知道  你因为滥用药物被停职了
I know that-- you were suspended on charges of substance abuse.
不管是不是急诊
Emergency or not,
Shephard医生  这里都没你的事
Dr. Shephard, you have no business being here.
我明白,我会对自己的行为负全部责任
I understand, And I take full responsibility for my actions.
不是的  医生
No, doctor.
是医院为你的行为负全部责任
The hospital takes full responsibility for your actions,
这让我们得对他们负责
And that makes us liable for them.
失陪
Excuse me.
-喂  -Jack  是我
- Hello? - Jack? It's me.
-Hurley  -Sayid到你那里了吗
- Hurley. - Hey, did sayid get to you? Did my dad drop him off?
-是的  Hurley  你在哪儿  -他还好吗
Yes. he did. hurley, where are-- is he okay?
-他很好  -太好了
- He's fine. - Awesome.
Hurley  你在哪儿
Hurley, where are you?
伙计  我很好  我在洛杉矶县监狱里
Dude, I'm totally cool. I'm in l.a. county lockup.
告诉Sayid我照他指示做的
Oh, and tell Sayid I did exactly what he said.
我很安全  Ben现在抓不到我了
I'm totally safe. ben's never gonna get me now.
你在说什么  Hurley  等等
What are you talking about, Hurley? wait! wait--
很好  你在这里  Sayid怎么样
Good. you're here. How's sayid?
给你用药
Got your meds for you.
对不起  我认为你走错房间了
Sorry, I think you have the wrong room.
没有
Nope.
133房间  是吗
Room 133, right?
这有医嘱  不过别担心
Got the orders right here. But don't worry.
不是给你打针
I won't have to give you an injection.
只是把药放到你的输液管里
Put this right in your i.v. line.
你是谁  你为谁干活
Who are you? Who are you working for?
-好了  说吧  说吧  -地址在我口袋里
- Okay, talk, talk. - Address--it's in my pocket.
Sayid
Hello, Sayid.
发生什么事情了
What happened?
谁住在Panorama Crest 42号
Do we know anyone who lives at 42 panorama crest?
是Kate的地址
That's Kate's address.
Kate  我是Jack  你还好吗
Kate? It's jack. Are you okay?
是的  我很好
Yeah. I'm fine.
你在哪里  家里吗
Where are you right now? are you at home?
什么
Uh... what?
你出来后我会给你解释
Listen, I'll explain everything once you're out,
但是你要带上Aaron...
But you've gotta get aaron--
听着  我不在家
Look, I'm not at home, okay? I'm...
Aaron在宾馆和Sun在一起
Aaron is at a hotel with sun.
Sun在洛杉矶吗
Sun? sun's in l.a.?
是的  她来办事
Yeah, she's here on business.
现在说话不太方便  Jack
Listen, jack, this is really not a good time.
我都不该接这个电话
I'm so sorry that I even picked up the phone.
Kate  别挂我电话  求你听着
Kate, do not hang up on me. please listen. listen, uh...
告诉我你在哪里好吗  我要见你
Will you tell me where you are? I need to see you?
Kate  拜托了
Kate, please.
我在市区
I'm downtown.
-威尔谢尔和奥利弗区  -好的  我马上到
- Wilshire and olive.  - okay. all right. I'm on my way.
她不在家  我这就去找她
She's not at home, but I'm gonna go to her right now.
好的  我去找Hugo
Good. I'll go deal with hugo.
想得美  Ben  我不会让你靠近他
Sorry, ben. I'm not letting you get anywhere near him.
你的朋友有难  我们要去救他们
You have friends in trouble. let's get them to safety
事后再说丑话吧
And save the dirty linen for later.
我来开车
I'll drive.
找到Kate之后
After you get kate,
在长滩码头  支路23号碰头
Meet us at the long beach marina, slip 23.
Jack  要抓紧  我们没时间了
And, jack... hurry. we're running out of time.
Locke
Hey, locke?
你要怎么和她说
What are you gonna say to her
对谁
Sorry?
Kate
Kate.
你怎么说服她回来
What are you gonna say to her to get her to come back?
我还没想好
I haven't figured that out yet.
告诉你吧
Well, let me tell you something.
她很兴奋
She was pretty excited
能跳上飞机离开这里
To hop on that chopper and get the hell out of here.
那是什么
What the hell is that?
不管是什么  离它远点
Whatever it is, we better stay clear of it.
海滩在这边
Beach is this way.
你想绕道观光吗
Now you wanna take the scenic route?
John
John...
你知道我们在什么时间吗
Do you know when we are?
我们得继续前进
We need to keep moving.
你的头还疼吗
Hey. how's your headache?
好些了
Better.
脚都走酸了  哪里顾得上头疼
Nothing like sore feet to take your mind off your head, eh?
别担心
Well, don't worry.
到了海边  我们就能坐上Zodiac
Once we get to the beach, we're gonna take the zodiac
去岛的另一边休息
Around the other side of the island and rest.
你真好  不过不用哄我  我没事
You're sweet, but you don't need to baby me. I'm fine.
没事吧
You okay?
我很好
I'm peachy.
又怎么了
Now what?
大家都别动
Nobody move.
-James  -我会小心
- James!  - I got this.
它知道我不想要它  会把它送走
It knows I don't want it, and I was gonna give it away.
婴儿都懂的
Babies know that stuff.
好吧  坚持住  听着
Okay, no, no, hang on. listen, listen.
你想要这孩子吗
Do you want this baby?
你希望它安全健康吗
Do you want it to be safe and healthy?
你不是一个人
You're not alone in this.
我们都关心你  这是我们大家的孩子
We are all here for you. this baby is all of ours.
我要你用力
But I need you to push.
好吗
Okay?
一  二  三
One, two, three...
用力  用力
Push! push!
加油  Claire  用力
Come on, claire! push!
好极了  要出来了
Aah! okay! he's coming!
用力  使劲
Push! push! push! push!
使劲  再用力
James
James?
怎么回事
What happened?
你看到什么了吗  James
Did you see something out here, james?
无所谓了
Don't matter.
已经消失了
It's gone now.
你刮胡子了
You shaved your beard.
是呀
Yeah.
想要改变一下
Just needed a change.
听着  Jack
Look, jack, uh...
我不知道你为什么来电话
I don't know why you called,
但我现在什么都做不了
But I can't be dealing with this right now.
出什么事了
What's going on?
没事  只是
Nothing. just...
-走吧  好吗  -为什么不告诉我
- Can you just go?  - why don't you just tell me?
Jack  求你走吧
Jack, please, just go.
Kate  告诉我
Kate, please, tell me.
有人想要Aaron
Somebody wants aaron.
什么
What?
有一个律师
There's a lawyer in there.
他的客户  他们知道我们在说谎
His clients-- they know we're lying.
他们知道我不是他妈妈
They know I'm not his mom,
要把他带走
And they're gonna take him away.
谁要把他带走
Who's gonna take him away?
你要干什么
What--what are you doing?
我得走了  你上不上车
Look, I gotta go, all right? get in or don't.
喂
Hey.
能告诉我你在那看见了谁吗
You ready to tell me who you saw back there?
我都说了  没什么
Already told you. it was nothin'.
我们都知道闪光之前的时间  James
You and I both know when we were before the flash, james.
你到底看见谁了
So who was it you saw?
Charlie  Shannon  还是你自己
Charlie? shannon? yourself?
你怎么会知道当时的时间  小Johnny
And how is it that you knew when we were, johnny boy?
那束光  是从舱门过来的  对吗
That light in the sky--it was from the hatch, wasn't it?
Boone死的那天晚上
The night that boone died...
我去了那里
I went out there
用尽全力的砸门
And started pounding on it as hard as I could.
我很困惑  很害怕
I was... confused... scared.
像个白痴一样说傻话
Babbling like an idiot,
问着  为什么要发生在我身上
Asking, why was all this happening to me?
找到答案了吗
Did you get an answer?
灯光亮起来  直射入空中
Light came on, shot up into the sky.
那时  我以为这有什么含义
At the time, I thought it meant something.
有吗
Did it?
没有  只是灯光
No. it was just a light.
你为什么带我们绕道
So why'd you turn us around then?
你不想回到那里吗
Don't you wanna go back there?
我干吗要那样做
Why would I wanna do that?
因此你就能说服自己做一些与众不同的事
So you could tell yourself to do things different,
脱离苦海
Save yourself a world of pain.
不  我需要这些痛苦来知道自己身处何地
No, I needed that pain to get to where I am now.
我刚刚流鼻血了
I just got a nosebleed.
什么  什么时候的事
What? when?
我们先别惊动到其他人  好吗
Let's just not freak out the others, okay?
告诉我
Just tell me...
-为什么她和我会这样  -我不知道
- Why--why her? why me? - I don't know.
我认为是和
Uh, I think it might have something to do
暴露在磁场的时间长短有关
With duration of exposure.
也就是你在岛上待的总时间
You know, the amount of time you've spent on the island.
这个解释说不通
Doesn't make any sense.
那群笨蛋已经在这里待了好几个月
Those yahoos have been here for months.
-我两个星期前才踏上这个岛的  -你确定吗
- I've never been here before two weeks ago. - Are you sure about that?
营地又回来了
The camp's back
总算到了
Finally.
有没有人想来瓶达摩啤酒
Anybody for a dharma beer?
有人吗  有人在吗
Hello? anybody here?
Rose  Bernard
我好奇这是什么时候发生的事情
I wonder how long ago this happened.
王八蛋
Son of a bitch!
这是什么
What is it?
是Vincent的
It's Vincent's.
是吗  那狗跑哪了
Yeah? well, where's the rest of the dog?
我们剩下的人哪去了
Where's the rest of our people?
Zodiac号也不见了
The Zodiac's gone, too.
也许你们其他的人把船开走了
Maybe your people took the boat.
到底为什么他们会那样做
Why the hell would they do that?
为了逃离乘这些玩意过来的人
To get away from whoever came in those.
这些玩意哪里来的
Where did these come from?
问得好
That's a good question.
看起来很古老
They're pretty old.
也没多古老
Not that old.
我看看
Let me see that.
"adg-uh-ruh"
adg-uh-ruh
Ajira  是个航空公司
Ajira. it's an airline.
是个印度航空公司  但飞往世界各地
It's based out of india, but they fly everywhere.
太好了,也许今晚他们有航班从这里飞往拉斯维加斯
Great. Maybe they got a flight out of here to vegas tonight.
乘这些船的是谁  还有其他人吗
-Who came in these? other others?
别看我
Don't look at me.
问题是  他们什么时候回来
My question is, when are they coming back?
我们别干等着  一起去搞清楚
Let's not wait to find out.
如果我们是开摩托艇
This plan sounded a hell of a lot better
这计划会感觉更好
When we were going by motorboat.
我们离那地方多远
How far is this place?
就在那个转角后头  就几个小时
It's around that point. not more than a couple hours.
噢  有意思了
Oh, joy.
你还好吗
You all right?
我看到Kate了
I saw Kate.
什么
What?
昨晚  在丛林里
Last night, in the jungle.
在上次闪光出现之前
Before the last flash.
她正在帮Claire接生
She was delivering Claire's baby.
但那是两个月之前的事了
But that was two months ago.
穿越时间真不是玩意
Time travel's a bitch.
趴下
Get down!
-我想他们是要把船抢回来  -加把劲
- I think they want their boat back! - Move!
-他们和你一伙的吗  -不  是你们的人吗
- These your people?! - No! are they yours?!
闭嘴  继续划
Shut up and keeping paddling!
没用  没用
Little help! little help!
划快点  他们越来越靠近了
Paddle harder! they're getting closer!
感谢上帝
Thank you,lord!
我收回刚刚说的话
I take that back!
大家往岸边划
Everybody, paddle! head for the shore!
Kate  那家伙告诉你
Kate, just because the guy
他准备去见他的客户
Told you that he was meeting his client
不代表他们就在洛杉矶
Doesn't mean that they're here in l.a.
他可能只是这么说来  来打发你
He could've just told you that to--to throw you off.
或者是他们现在就在那个宾馆里头
Or they're in that hotel right now.
好吧  就算你说的是对的
Okay. and what if they are?
如果那个想夺走Aaron的人
What if the person who wants to take aaron
就坐在宾馆里
Is sitting in that hotel room right now?
又怎么样
Then what?
拜托  和我一起走
Come on. come with me.
我们先接走Aaron
We'll--we'll go get aaron,
然后再想办法
We'll put our heads together, and we'll figure something out.
好吧
All right.
我的天啊
Oh, my god.
是Claire的母亲
It's Claire's mother.
等等
Wait.
-我还等什么  Jack  -等等  我只是
- What am I waiting for, Jack? - Wait. I just...
-我们先整理下头绪  -她知道了
- Let's just think about this for a minute. - She knows.
也许她还不知道
Maybe she doesn't know.
不  但她知道Aaron的存在  这就够要命的了
No, but she knows about aaron, and that's all that matters!
我去和她谈谈
Let me go talk to her.
什么
What?
如果我能向她解释清楚这么做的原因
If I can just explain to her why we did it--
也许我可能让她明白事情的缘由
Maybe if I can get her to understand why...
她会听我的
She'll listen to me.
我能处理好的  Kate  我会处理好的
I can fix this, kate. I can fix it.
Aaron也是我的家人
Aaron is my family, too.
Shephard医生
Dr. Shephard?
你好  Littleton女士
Hello, Ms. Littleton. um...
我能进来吗
May I come in?
当然
Of course.
你全身都淋湿了
You look drenched.
不  不  不  我没事
No, no. no, I'm fine.
天啊  自从你父亲的葬礼后我们就没再见过面
God, I haven't seen you since your father's funeral.
你怎么知道我在这的
How did you even know I was here?
我知道你在这里  Littleton女士
I knew you were here, Ms. Littleton,
是因为我跟踪了你的律师
Because I followed your lawyer.
你为什么要这样做
Why would you do that?
我这样做是因为
I'm--i did it because, um...
我理解你为什么想这样做
I understand that you feel the need to do this.
但是我希望你能明白
But I need you to know
我和Kate做的一切事情  都是为了Aaron
That everything that kate and I have done--it was for aaron.
谁是Aaron
Who's... Aaron?
我恐怕不是很明白你在说什么
I-i'm afraid I'm not following you.
littleton女士
Ms. littleton, um...
你在洛杉矶干什么
What are you doing here in los angeles?
走  开车  给sun打电话
Let's go. drive. then call sun
告诉她把Aaron带到长滩码头
And tell her to bring aaron to the long beach marina.
你在说什么  发生什么了
what--wh-what are you talking about? what happened?
Kate我们现在必须要走了
Kate, we have to go now.
我哪儿也不去  除非你告诉我发生什么事了
I'm not going anywhere until yo tell me what just happened!
她什么都不知道
She doesn't know anything.
什么
What?
她不知道
She doesn't know.
她一直以为Claire已经死了
She still thinks that claire is dead.
她甚至也不知道Aaron的存在
She doesn't even know that aaron exists.
-但律师  -她起诉了大洋航空
-But the lawyer-- -she sued oceanic,
她来城里打点行装
And she's in town to pick up her settlement.
如果她的律师和要带走我儿子的人
What, and it's just a coincidence that her lawyer
碰巧是同一个人呢
Happens to be the same one that's trying to take my son?
我不知道
I don't know.
但不管是谁想带走Aaron
But whoever's trying to take aaron...
绝对不会是她
It's not her.
那是谁呢
Then who is it?
我可以问你些问题吗
Can I ask you something?
你为什么救Hugo呢
Why'd you take it upon yourself to rescue hugo?
我必须要确保Hurley的安全
I had to make sure hurley was safe.
你可以在这边停车
You can pull in over here.
Linus先生
Mr. linus.
Norton先生
Mr. norton.
我调查过了
I looked into it,
他们没什么针对Reyes的具体案件
And they don't have any kind of solid case against reyes.
法医称在Santa Rosa外发现的那个男人
The m.e. said that the man found outside santa rosa
在Reyes逃跑前已被杀害
Was killed before reyes escaped.
这真是个好消息
That's very good news.
我们今天上午有个预备听证会
We have a prelim hearing in the morning.
法官不会让这通过的
The judge will never let it get past that,
Reyes会无罪释放的
And reyes will be a free man.
Dan  谢谢你
Thank you, dan.
不客气
Anytime.
他是谁
Who was that?
那是我的律师
That's my lawyer.
好了
Aah! okay!
别让我再做这样的事了
Remind me never to do that again.
-我们在哪  -天亮前说不清
-Where are we? -it's hard to say till it gets light.
我们还没机会把上次的话说完
We didn't get a chance to finish our conversation.
什么谈话
What conversation was that?
他们开始射杀我们前的谈话
The one before they started shooting at us,
你准备告诉我再次见到kate的感受
Where you were about to tell me how it felt to see kate again.
我没打算告诉你什么
I wasn't about to tell you anything.
为什么现在不告诉我呢
Why don't you tell me now?
我都可以碰到她了
I was close enough to touch her.
如果我想做  我本可以
If I wanted to, I could've...
站出来和她说话的
Stood right up and talked to her.
为什么不呢
Why didn't you?
反正事情都已经发生了
What's done is done.
怎么了
What's wrong?
过来看看这个
Come and look at this!
这是些残骸
It's wreckage.
像才坠毁的样子
Looks like it just happened.
有人会说法语吗
Anybody speak french?
Jack  干嘛今天打电话给我
Jack, why did you call me today?
我跟你说过了
I told you. I s...
我很担心
I was worried.
为什么你要担心  为什么是今天
But why? why were you worried? why today?
我不
I don't...
我打给你之前  Sayid被人袭击了
Right before I called you, sayid was attacked.
那人的口袋里有你的地址
And the guy that did it-- your address was in his pocket.
Sayid  他在这做什么
Sayid? what's he doing here?
这些现在不重要了
That's not important right now.
重要的是我们把你和Aaron转移到安全的地方
What matters is that we get you and aaron someplace safe.
躲谁
Safe from who?
Kate
Hello, kate.
没事的  他和我一起的
It's okay. he's with me.
他和你是一起的吗
He's with you?
我知道这很难解释
I know this is gonna be hard to understand,
但他是来帮助我们的
But he's here to help us.
来帮助我们丢下的每一个人
To help everyone that we left behind.
-我们得再次集合起来  -是他
- We all need to be together again. - it's him.
什么
What?
他就是想抢走Aaron的人
It's him. he's the one who's trying to take aaron.
-不  你不明白  -不  Jack  她是对的
- No. no. you-- you don't understand. - no, jack. she's right.
是我
It was me.
对不起
Sorry.
你以为你是谁
Who the hell do you think you are?
为什么你就不能滚远点
Why don't you just stay away?!
为什么你就不能放过我们母子
Why don't you leave me and my son alone?!
因为他不是你儿子  Kate
Because he's not your son, kate.
4  8  Robert
15  16
15... 16...
听不懂
No understand.
你会说英语
You speak english?
一点点
Little.
你还好吧
Are you okay?
还好
Yes.
你怎么来到这儿的
How did you get here?
-船  -坐什么[法语]
- Boat. - qui est-ce?
什么船
What boat?
消失了
It's gone.
沉了
Sink.
肯定是风暴引起的  就跟我们一样
It must've been caught in the same storm as ours.
你是谁  你在水里多长时间了
Who are you? how long you in the water?
我不知道  你怎么会不知道
I don't know. how do you not know
那你怎么会漂浮在海中央的
How you wound up in the middle of the ocean, ah?
Montand
Montand...
谢谢
Thank you.
你叫什么名字
What is your name?
Jin
你好  Jin  我是Danielle  Danielle Rousseau
You know, Jin, I'm Danielle, Danielle Rousseau